https://www.holidayleds.com/privacy-policy

1.  Information Collection and Use
HolidayLEDs.com (Us or We) is the sole owner of information collected on this site to purchase most products and services from HolidayLEDs.com (refer to the next paragraph for the limited exceptions to this). We will not sell, share, or rent this information to any third parties, except as outlined in this policy. We collect information from our customers to process orders and better serve you with pertinent information, such as order confirmations, order status updates, and to provide you with information on products and services that are available from us. We may also use such information to better understand the shopping experiences of you individually or in conjunction with a group of our customers. Information collected includes your name, shipping address, billing address, telephone numbers, e-mail address, and payment information such as your credit card number. We also require you to submit a username and password of your choice for your future access to your account information. To safeguard that your user name and password remain confidential, DO NOT share this information with anyone. We may also use your email address to send you our newsletter, transactional communications, informational emails regarding changes in our policies, or changes in our methods of conducting business.
2.
Registration
In order to process your orders placed on this website, you must first complete the registration form. During registration, you will be required to provide your contact information, which includes your name, e-mail address, telephone number and street address. This information is used to provide you with important HolidayLEDs.com services such as automated order status updates via e-mail.
Your email will not be sold or shared with any third parties.
We do send out approximately 10 email newsletters each year.
If you do not wish to receive these emails you can opt out.
3.
Order
Most of the information collected in the registration process will be used to process orders. During the order process, you will have to provide credit card information such as your credit card number, expiration date, and CVV code. This information is used for billing purposes and to fulfill your order. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this contact information to get in touch with you. To properly process your credit card information, we must share your personal and financial information with the merchant bank for authorization and approval. This process is protected by an enhanced security system. Our system is set up to purge all credit card information as soon as the approved charge is completed.
We do not keep your credit card information.
4.
Cookies
We customize certain content based upon your browser type and other information provided by our cookie. If you choose to reject the cookie, you can still browse our store but will be unable to use the shopping cart to buy merchandise. The HolidayLEDs.com shopping cart cannot function without cookies enabled so that the necessary information to process your order is retained. If you disable cookies, HolidayLEDs.com will be unable to accept your online order. We will not share any personally identifiable information provided by this cookie with any third party. We will, however, link data stored in cookies to the personally identifiable information you submitted while on our site.
This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by HolidayLEDs.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
5.
Log Files
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information, and we do not distribute or share IP information with any third parties.
6.
Data Sharing
We may employ third party companies to perform functions on our behalf. These functions may include order fulfillment, package delivery, marketing assistance, postal and e-mail delivery, customer service, data analysis, and credit processing. The third parties we contract for these purposes have limited access to your personal information and may not use it for other purposes.
Under no circumstances will we sell your personal information to any third party.
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information i) as required by law, ii) when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site, iii) when we believe that your actions violate applicable laws, iv) when we believe that your actions violate HolidayLEDs.com's terms and conditions that you agree to by using, accessing or purchasing from or through www.HolidayLEDs.com (or its affiliated websites), v) when we believe that your actions violate any usage guidelines for specific products or services, vi) when we believe that your actions violate or threaten the rights, property, or safety of our company, our users, or others, or (vii) when you consent to allow your personally identifiable information to be shared or disclosed.
Be aware that when you volunteer information or create a public profile in the course of your participation in our community features such as forums, comments, or other forms of public communication and interaction, you are also agreeing to allow certain aspects of your personally identifiable information to be made public.
7.
Third Party Service Providers Disclosure
We may use PayPal or similar service providers to facilitate our order and payment processing. When you place an order, you may be automatically transferred to PayPal's or another third-party provider's web site. Please be aware that their privacy policy governs the use and collection of your personally identifiable information and is shared with us to fulfill the order.
8.
Comments, Articles, Postings and Other Posts
Published user comments are genuine, but HolidayLEDs.com reserves the right to edit or alter such to remove personal information, statements that may be a violation of law, or statements that may infringe on the rights of HolidayLEDs.com or third parties. HolidayLEDs.com reserves the right to post or remove any comment at its discretion.
By posting your comment(s) or posting(s) on our website , you give us permission to reprint or use the posting in connection with our businesses (including but not limited to the marketing and selling of various products and services, as well as the marketing of HolidayLEDs.com). You also are agreeing to the following: (1) The reprint or use of the Posting will be at our discretion and without compensation to you; (2) We may use the Posting with or without any pseudo (pen) name credit; (3) Our right to use the Posting is perpetual and may be assigned by us; (4) We may use the Posting locally, nationally or globally and such use may be made in any media, information or communication platform (including Internet advertising) currently in use or later developed; (5) You and not someone else composed and posted the Posting; (6) HolidayLEDs.com may allow any of its parents, subsidiaries or affiliates to use the Posting in the same manner as set forth herein but in relation to their businesses and websites; and (7) We may edit or alter such Posting to remove personal information, statements that may be a violation of law, or statements that may infringe on the rights of HolidayLEDs.com or third parties.
Other than your pseudo (pen) name, which we may or may not use, your personal contact information will not be disclosed in connection with our reprint or use of your Posting.
9.
Links
HolidayLEDs.com may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that HolidayLEDs.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this website.
10.
Security
HolidayLEDs.com takes precautions to protect its customers' information. When you submit personal information via the website, we follow policies and procedures designed to protect your information both online and offline.
Any information you provide us through this site is protected by AES 256 byte SSL encryption.
All HolidayLEDs.com servers, including web servers and database servers, are housed and maintained in secure locations. Access to the database is strictly monitored and protected from outside access. Internet access is restricted and protected by multiple firewalls. The servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secured environment, inside a secured and locked room.
11.
Updating/Reviewing Personal Information
Customers may change or review their stored account information such as street address or e-mail address through our website by logging into their account. You must have your username and password in order to access your account.
×
OK
